{
    "StartingQuestions": [
        [1, 7, 13, 18, 23],
        {
            "id": 1,
            "type": "mc",
            "question": "How was my day?",
            "choices": [
                {
                    "answer": "Amazing!",
                    "output": "My day was amazing!",
                    "targetid": 2,
                    "picked": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Good!",
                    "output": "My day was pretty good,",
                    "targetid": 3,
                    "picked": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Alright.",
                    "output": "My day was ok,",
                    "targetid": 4,
                    "picked": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Not great.",
                    "output": "My day was Bad.",
                    "targetid": 5,
                    "picked": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Absolutely awful...",
                    "output": "My day was absolutely awful...",
                    "targetid": 6,
                    "picked": 0
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "The best thing that happened today was",
            "title": "An incredible day"
        },
        {
            "id": 3,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "I was able to do",
            "title": "Good vibes"
        },
        {
            "id": 4,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "It was an average day because",
            "title": "Just another average day"
        },
        {
            "id": 5,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "Today wasn't great because",
            "title": "Today was not the day"
        },
        {
            "id": 6,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "The worst part of it was",
            "title": "I don't want to remember today"
        },
        {
            "id": 7,
            "type": "mc",
            "question": "How productive was I today?",
            "choices": [
                {
                    "answer": "I was a machine!",
                    "output": "Productivity today was far above what I hoped for!",
                    "targetid": 8,
                    "picked": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Great!",
                    "output": "My productivity today was as great!",
                    "targetid": 9,
                    "picked": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Alright.",
                    "output": "My productivity today was decent",
                    "targetid": 10,
                    "picked": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Not great",
                    "output": "My productivity today was not great,",
                    "targetid": 11,
                    "picked": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Negative, I'm worse off than before",
                    "output": "My productivity today was awful, I'm worse off than before.",
                    "targetid": 12,
                    "picked": 0
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 8,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "Today, I wasn't expecting to be able to do",
            "title": "No play, all work"
        },
        {
            "id": 9,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "I was able to get tasks done because",
            "title": "A productive day"
        },
        {
            "id": 10,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "overall, the day felt",
            "title": "Another average day"
        },
        {
            "id": 11,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "I was unproductive because",
            "title": "No motivation today"
        },
        {
            "id": 12,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "I wish that I didn't",
            "title": "I'm going downhill"
        },
        {
            "id": 13,
            "type": "mc",
            "question": "Which best describes my mental health today?",
            "choices": [
                {
                    "answer": "Amazing!",
                    "output": "Today, my mental health was amazing!",
                    "targetid": 14,
                    "picked": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Pretty Good!",
                    "output": "My mental health was good today!",
                    "targetid": 15,
                    "picked": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Alright.",
                    "output": "Today, I felt a little blue.",
                    "targetid": 16,
                    "picked": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Could use some work.",
                    "output": "My mental health wasn't great today,",
                    "targetid": 17,
                    "picked": 0
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 14,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "I felt great today because",
            "title": "A day full of joy"
        },
        {
            "id": 15,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "I kept up my mental health by",
            "title": "I felt good today"
        },
        {
            "id": 16,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "My mental health was not great today becuase",
            "title": "Too much stress today"
        },
        {
            "id": 17,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "I plan on improving by",
            "title": "Today was not a good day"
        },
        {
            "id": 18,
            "type": "mc",
            "question": "Did anything out of the ordinary happen today?",
            "choices": [
                {
                    "answer": "Something amazing!",
                    "output": "Guess what happened today?",
                    "targetid": 19,
                    "picked": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Something awful!",
                    "output": "Something awful happened today...",
                    "targetid": 20,
                    "picked": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Something strange?",
                    "output": "I saw the strangest thing,",
                    "targetid": 21,
                    "picked": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Basically nothing.",
                    "output": "Nothing abnormal today;",
                    "targetid": 22,
                    "picked": 0
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 19,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "I couldn't believe my eyes,",
            "title": "An amazing day"
        },
        {
            "id": 20,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "I was shocked to find out",
            "title": "Not a lucky day"
        },
        {
            "id": 21,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "I've never seen anything like it! Today,",
            "title": "Today was no ordinary day"
        },
        {
            "id": 22,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "I didn't see anything interesting because",
            "title": "Nothing out of the ordinary"
        },
        {
            "id": 23,
            "type": "mc",
            "question": "How was the weather?",
            "choices": [
                {
                    "answer": "Sunny and pleasent!",
                    "output": "Really nice day today.",
                    "targetid": 24,
                    "picked": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer": "It rained.",
                    "output": "It was a bit yucky out today.",
                    "targetid": 25,
                    "picked": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Cloudy, but no rain.",
                    "output": "Skies were a bit dark today.",
                    "targetid": 26,
                    "picked": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Snow!",
                    "output": "It's a winter wonderland!",
                    "targetid": 27,
                    "picked": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Snow.",
                    "output": "It's freezing out.",
                    "targetid": 28,
                    "picked": 0
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 24,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "Today I went to",
            "title": "Sun times fun times"
        },
        {
            "id": 25,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "Indoors today I did",
            "title": "Wet day"
        },
        {
            "id": 26,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "Today I did",
            "title": "Chill day"
        },
        {
            "id": 27,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "Today I went out in the snow and",
            "title": "Super fun day!"
        },
        {
            "id": 28,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "I kept warm by",
            "title": "It was freezing"
        },
        {
            "id": 29,
            "type": "mc",
            "question": "",
            "choices": [
                {
                    "answer": "It was a holiday!",
                    "output": "It's finally that time of year.",
                    "targetid": 30,
                    "picked": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer": "There was an event!",
                    "output": "Today was exciting,",
                    "targetid": 31,
                    "picked": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Something happened to me!",
                    "output": "Something exciting happened to me today,",
                    "targetid": 32,
                    "picked": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer": "It's the weekend!",
                    "output": "TGIF amarite?",
                    "targetid": 33,
                    "picked": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Nope, Normal weekday.",
                    "output": "Is it Friday yet?",
                    "targetid": 34,
                    "picked": 0
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 30,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "Today is",
            "title": "It's that time of year!"
        },
        {
            "id": 31,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "I participated in",
            "title": "Good times"
        },
        {
            "id": 32,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "I was shocked when",
            "title": "Exciting times!"
        },
        {
            "id": 33,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "This weekend I plan to",
            "title": "Super fun weekend"
        },
        {
            "id": 34,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "This weekend I plan to",
            "title": "Keep on keeping on"
        }
    ],
    "FinalQuestions": [
        [1, 2, 3, 4, 8],
        {
            "id": 1,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "If I could sum up today in one word, what would it be?",
            "output": "Overall, I would describe today as"
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "What am I most looking forward to tomorrow?",
            "output": "I can't wait for tomorrow, I'm going to"
        },
        {
            "id": 3,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "What is something small that I am thankful for today?",
            "output": "At the end of the day, I am thankful for"
        },
        {
            "id": 4,
            "type": "mc",
            "question": "Energy wise, how do I feel?",
            "choices": [
                {
                    "answer": "Amazing",
                    "output": "In terms of energy, I feel amazing!",
                    "targetid": 5,
                    "picked": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Normal",
                    "output": "In terms of energy, I feel normal;",
                    "targetid": 6,
                    "picked": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Exhausted.",
                    "output": "I'm absolutely exhausted.",
                    "targetid": 7,
                    "picked": 0
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 5,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "I'm glad that I was able to",
            "output": "I'm glad that I was able to"
        },
        {
            "id": 6,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "today wasn't too special because",
            "output": "today wasn't too special because"
        },
        {
            "id": 7,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "The most tiring thing today was",
            "output": "The most tiring thing today was"
        },
        {
            "id": 8,
            "type": "mc",
            "question": "Would I consider today to be a success?",
            "choices": [
                {
                    "answer": "For sure!",
                    "output": "Today was definitely a success;",
                    "targetid": 9,
                    "picked": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Yeah",
                    "output": "Today was successful, yeah.",
                    "targetid": 10,
                    "picked": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Not really",
                    "output": "Today wasn't really what I was hoping for,",
                    "targetid": 11,
                    "picked": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Definitely not",
                    "output": "I failed everything today.",
                    "targetid": 12,
                    "picked": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Success is a social construct",
                    "output": "I would talk about how successful I was, but success is a social construct;",
                    "targetid": 13,
                    "picked": 0
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 9,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "What do I feel the most acomplished about?",
            "output": "I feel the most acomplished about"
        },
        {
            "id": 10,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "What did I enjoy doing?",
            "output": "I enjoyed doing"
        },
        {
            "id": 11,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "What did I miss doing?",
            "output": "I wasn't able to do"
        },
        {
            "id": 12,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "Why did I not get anything done?",
            "output": "I am a failture because"
        },
        {
            "id": 13,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "Why is success a social construct?",
            "output": "this is because"
        }
    ],
    "MainQuestions": [
        [1, 5, 6, 7, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 26],
        {
            "id": 1,
            "type": "mc",
            "question": "Was I attacked by a Canada goose?",
            "choices": [
                {
                    "answer": "Many times",
                    "output": "I barely survived all the geese attacks,",
                    "targetid": 2,
                    "picked": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Just once",
                    "output": "A goose tried to nibble me today,",
                    "targetid": 3,
                    "picked": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer": "I don't go outside",
                    "output": "Canadian geese make me too scared to go outside.",
                    "targetid": 4,
                    "picked": 0
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "If I see a goose again, I'll",
            "output": "If I see a goose again, I'll"
        },
        {
            "id": 3,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "It tried to bite my",
            "output": "It tried to bite my"
        },
        {
            "id": 4,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "I'd rather stay inside,",
            "output": "I'd rather stay inside,"
        },
        {
            "id": 5,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "What was the best thing I did today?",
            "output": "The best thing I did today was"
        },
        {
            "id": 6,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "How much rain was there today?",
            "output": "In terms of rain, there was"
        },
        {
            "id": 7,
            "type": "mc",
            "question": "Did I go outside today?",
            "choices": [
                {
                    "answer": "No",
                    "output": "I didn't leave the house today,",
                    "targetid": 8,
                    "picked": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Just for a short walk",
                    "output": "I went out for a quick walk.",
                    "targetid": 9,
                    "picked": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer": "To go to work",
                    "output": "I went out to work,",
                    "targetid": 10,
                    "picked": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer": "To do vigorous exercise",
                    "output": "I burned lots of calories today,",
                    "targetid": 11,
                    "picked": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Other",
                    "output": "I went outside today,",
                    "targetid": 12,
                    "picked": 0
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 8,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "this was because",
            "output": "this was because"
        },
        {
            "id": 9,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "The walk was",
            "output": "The walk was"
        },
        {
            "id": 10,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "work was",
            "output": "work was"
        },
        {
            "id": 11,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "I exercised at",
            "output": "I exercised at"
        },
        {
            "id": 12,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "I went to",
            "output": "I went to"
        },
        {
            "id": 13,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "What hobbies did I spend time on today?",
            "output": "For hobbies, I did"
        },
        {
            "id": 14,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "What did I eat today?",
            "output": "Today I filled my wittle tum-tum with"
        },
        {
            "id": 15,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "What friends did I talk to today?",
            "output": "Today, I talked to my friends"
        },
        {
            "id": 16,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "What did I get done that I've been putting off?",
            "output": "I've been procrastinating for a while, but finally finished"
        },
        {
            "id": 17,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "What do I plan on doing tomorrow?",
            "output": "Tomorrow, I plan on"
        },
        {
            "id": 18,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "What did I say that I would do yesterday?",
            "output": "Yesterday, I said that I would"
        },
        {
            "id": 19,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "When part of the day was I the happiest?",
            "output": "Today, I was very happy when"
        },
        {
            "id": 20,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "What was a challenging thing I experienced today?",
            "output": "I experienced difficulties when"
        },
        {
            "id": 21,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "What did I do in my down time?",
            "output": "For my down time today, I decided to"
        },
        {
            "id": 22,
            "type": "mc",
            "question": "Did I stay connected to my family today?",
            "choices": [
                {
                    "answer": "Yes, we talked a lot",
                    "output": "We talked a lot,",
                    "targetid": 23,
                    "picked": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer": "We connected a little bit",
                    "output": "We had a quick conversation,",
                    "targetid": 24,
                    "picked": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer": "No",
                    "output": "I didn't contact my family today,",
                    "targetid": 25,
                    "picked": 0
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 23,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "we chatted about",
            "output": "we chatted about"
        },
        {
            "id": 24,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "the conversation was about",
            "output": "the conversation was about"
        },
        {
            "id": 25,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "this was because",
            "output": "this was because"
        },
        {
            "id": 26,
            "type": "mc",
            "question": "What did I clean today?",
            "choices": [
                {
                    "answer": "I cleaned my house!",
                    "output": "I cleaned my house today,",
                    "targetid": 27,
                    "picked": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer": "I washed my car!",
                    "output": "I washed my car today,",
                    "targetid": 28,
                    "picked": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer": "I took a shower!",
                    "output": "I took a shower today,",
                    "targetid": 29,
                    "picked": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer": "I'm a filthy human being...",
                    "output": "I didn't clean anything today,",
                    "targetid": 30,
                    "picked": 0
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 27,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "My house was extremely",
            "output": "it was really"
        },
        {
            "id": 28,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "My car was covered in",
            "output": "it was covered in"
        },
        {
            "id": 29,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "I smelled really",
            "output": "this was because I smelled really"
        },
        {
            "id": 30,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "This was because",
            "output": "this was because"
        }
    ],
    "Formats": [
        {
            "id": 1,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "",
            "output": ""
        },

        {
            "id": 1,
            "type": "mc",
            "question": "",
            "choices": [
                {
                    "answer": "",
                    "output": "",
                    "targetid": 1,
                    "picked": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer": "",
                    "output": "",
                    "targetid": 1,
                    "picked": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer": "",
                    "output": "",
                    "targetid": 1,
                    "picked": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer": "",
                    "output": "",
                    "targetid": 1,
                    "picked": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer": "",
                    "output": "",
                    "targetid": 1,
                    "picked": 0
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 1,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "",
            "output": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 1,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "",
            "output": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 1,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "",
            "output": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 1,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "",
            "output": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 1,
            "type": "written",
            "question": "",
            "output": ""
        }
    ]
}